healthtrioconnect.com 2019-01-01

# None

Return to Login

Your privacy is important to us. In order to better help you protect your privacy we have provided this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about how your information is collected and used. HealthTrio's number one priority is to provide the tools that enhance productivity while protecting your right to privacy. We understand that health care is a very personal, and private subject and recognize the fact that it is our responsibility to maintain the privacy of our Users. This privacy statement will inform you of the information that we collect, how it is protected, and what choices you have on how it is used. We ask that you read this policy to better understand our commitment to you and your privacy.

## Cookies

HealthTrio uses cookies to facilitate the sign-in process for you across multiple applications on the site. Cookies give users a special, random ID that is a small text file, which is stored on the hard drive of a user's computer. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Please note: Nothing in a cookie allows anyone to identify you individually. Your computer is assigned a number and that number is stored using the cookie. This number is only meaningful in the context of our secure database system and your personalized version of **_connect_ **. 

## Interactive Areas

HealthTrio is not responsible for information that is voluntarily provided by the user in interactive areas (i.e. discussion groups, message boards, on-line chats). Information divulged through these mediums may in fact increase future solicitations by people or companies not affiliated with HealthTrio. Be aware that you are in public forum and adjust your actions appropriately.

## Links

HealthTrio provides links to other Internet sites maintained by third parties. When you click on these links, you are moving to another web site. Please be aware that HealthTrio is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. HealthTrio encourages our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statement of each and every site, as their polices may be different than ours. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the **_connect_ ** web site. 

## Log Files

HealthTrio employs user ID to analyze trends, and audit application use for performance purposes.

## Registration

In order to use the **_connect_ ** website, each user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give the following contact information: 

  * Company
  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Position
  * Phone and Facsimile Number

This information is intended to support our health plans, their members, and providers by authorizing user access to the site and to enable user contact regarding services and features available on this site. It is not used for any other purposes; the data is not sold.

## Security

To prevent unauthorized access and maintain data integrity, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. HealthTrio uses industry-standard transport layer encryption to ensure secure end-to-end communications.

## Notification of Changes

Any changes to HealthTrio's privacy policy will be posted on our website so our users can always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time we intend to use personal information in a manner different from what was stated when it was collected, we will first notify the user by way of email. The user will maintain the right to decide if we are allowed to use the information in this manner. We will only use collected data in accordance with the privacy policy that was in effect at the time the information was collected.

If at any time you believe that this site has not adhered to the aforementioned policy or you have a question, please feel free to contact us by emailing: [privacy@healthtrio.com](mailto:privacy@healthtrio.com "Email: privacy@healthtrio.com")
